Guide tot he Yale College Records Concerning Teaching Fellows
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College records concerning teaching fellows
1983-1986
RU 574
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.75
(5 boxes)
The records consist of appointments, correspondence, and financial records documenting departmental teaching fellows at Yale College.
Yale College (1887- )
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 9-E (YRG 9-E), Records documenting Yale College offices, programs, and projects.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of appointments, correspondence, and financial records documenting departmental teaching fellows at Yale College.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Graduate teaching assistants; Yale College (1887- ); Yale University -- Students
- Records concerning teaching fellows, 1983-1984; Accession 1986-A-106
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020.
  - Afro-American Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 2A)
  - Astronomy, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Biology, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Classics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Computer Science, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - East Asian Languages and Literatures, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Economics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Engineering and Applied Science, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - English, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - French, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Geology and Geophysics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - German, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - History, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - History of Art, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Humanities, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Italian, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Linguistics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Literature Major, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mathematics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Hedieval Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Music, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Near Eastern Languages ,and Literatures, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Philosophy, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Physics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Political Science, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Psychology, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Religious Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Renaissance Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Residential College Seminars, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sociology, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Spanish, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Statistics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Theatre Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Homen's Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Yale College Dean's Office, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Appointment Forms and Correspondence, 1984-1985; Accession 1987-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021.
  - Teaching Fellows and PTAIS--correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Sciences 687H/685A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Afro-American Studies 566A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arnerican Studies 565A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Anthropology 591A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Astronomy 620A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Biology 615A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chemistry 921A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Classics 567A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Computer Science 622A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - DeVane Lectures 672A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - East Asian Languages and literatures 569A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Economics 592A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Engineering 650A, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - English 570A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Epidemiology and Public Health, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - French 571A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Geology and Geophysics 625A., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - German 573A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - History 574A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - History of Art 575A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Humanities 672A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Italian 582A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Linguistics 596A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Literature 679A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Henry Luce Lectures 589A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mathematics 626A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Medieval Studies 576A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemisty 6l6A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Music 577A, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures 578A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Philosophy 579A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Physics 627A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Political Science 597A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Psychology 598A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Religious Studies 580A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Renaissance Studies 583A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Residential College Semtnars 677A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures 581A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Sociology 599A-31, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - School of Organization and Management, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Spanish 572A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Statistics 600A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Teacher Preparation 642A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Theatre Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Wilderness/Wagner 675A-32-12312, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Voyager Fund 675A-32-67820, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Women's Studies 672A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Writing Intensive 990A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Writing Intensive Program/Pew Grant 990A, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Records concerning teaching fellows, 1985-1986; Accession 1988-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022.
  - Afro-American Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anthropology, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Astronomy, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Biology, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chemistry, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Classics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Computer Science, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - East Asian Languages & Literature, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Economics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Engineering & Applied Science, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - English, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Epidemiology & Public Health, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - French, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Geology & Geophysics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - German, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - History, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - History of Art, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - History of Science, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Humanities, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Italian, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Linguistics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Literature, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Mathematics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Medieval Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Molecular Biophysics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Music, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Near East Languages & Literature, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Philosophy, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Physics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Political Science, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Psychology, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Religious Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Renaissance Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Residential College Seminars, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Slavic, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Sociology, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Spanish, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Theater Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Women's Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Dean's Office, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)